* Solutions
* Plans and Add-ons
* Partners
* Support

Search    

**Our Company Privacy Policy**
==============================

_This Privacy Policy was last updated on Febuary 1st 2024._

We have made this policy short and easy to read and to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) [2016/679](https://eur-lex.europa.eu/eli/reg/2016/679/oj) (GDPR).

Unless we link to a different policy or state otherwise, this Privacy Policy applies when you visit or use the Robotel website, applications, APIs, or other related services. By using our services, you consent to such use of your information and Personal Data and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

The data protection principle applies to all data entered by visitors to any Robotel website, by an institution about their students, and teachers. It also applies to data recordings generated by the Robotel programs and stored in the database.

This privacy policy will explain how Robotel uses the personal data we collect from you when you use our website.

Topics:

--------------------------------------------------------

If you are only browsing our website, we collect the same basic information that most websites collect. We use common internet tools such as cookies, web server logs, and analytics services to gather the data. Some of these tools offer you the ability to opt out of data collection. We collect from everyone, whether they have a Robotel account or not. Our Company collects the following data:

* Personal identification information (full name, email address, geolocation, school establishment)
* Login identification information (email address, passwords)
* Optional personal identification information (job title, phone number, message)

If you (or your institution's administrators) have created an account, we require some basic information at the time of account creation. This includes either your username, or your name, or your email address, and your password.

We collect this information to create your account and provide services to you. We use your information to identify you in our programs so that we can provide you with information about scores and activities in exercises in the SmartClass programs. We may use your email address to communicate further with you. 

------------------------------------------------------------

You directly provide Robotel with most of the data we collect. We collect data and process data when you:

* Register online or place an order for any of our products or services.
* Voluntarily complete a customer survey or provide feedback on any of our message boards or via email.
* Use or view our website via your browser’s cookies.

------------------------------------------------------------

All data is available to a limited number of Robotel staff for support, research, and development work. We do not allow any outside parties to access the database. Any personal information provided by you is used only to help us provide a better service to you and for us to identify your needs and requirements.

Robotel collects your data so that we can:

* Process your order, manage your account.
* Email you with special offers on other products and services we think you might like.
* Give you access to our different services

------------------------------------------------------------

Robotel securely stores your data at a web provider. We are using HostGator and Google servers. For sensitive data like passwords, we use encryption functions.

We use appropriate security based on the type and sensitivity of data being stored. As with any internet-enabled system, there is always a risk of unauthorized access, so it's important to protect passwords and to contact us if you suspect any unauthorized access to your account.

A teacher's access is restricted to data on students in their group only. An account administrator can see all the details for that account.

When a user is deleted from the system, all records relating to that user are deleted.

----------------------------------------------------------

We keep personal information only for as long as required for the purposes for which it's supplied. Where your information is no longer required, we will always make sure it is disposed of or anonymized safely and securely.

For institutional accounts, data is kept for access by the administrator and other licensed parties within the institution for as long as the license is valid and the user account is active. Where the user account becomes inactive, data will be deleted or anonymized for a maximum of one year after the last login. An administrator can delete data at any time, which will cause it to be permanently and safely destroyed.

Where an institutional license lapses or terminates, data is kept for up to a year. This is so that it can be restored to the system should the institution choose to renew its subscription. After a maximum of a year, the data will be deleted or anonymized.

---------------------------------

The use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google’s APIs to our SmartClass by Robotel platform will adhere to the [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes) including the Limited Use requirements.

SmartClass by Robotel will use the [https://www.googleapis.com/auth/calendar.events](https://www.googleapis.com/auth/calendar.events) scope to create, update and delete a user's Google calendar events that pertain directly to the ‘Go Live’ part of the SmartClass application. The users will be able to manage their ‘Go Live’ events through the SmartClass by Robotel application which will then sync with their Google calendar. The events created are linked to a class and the meeting link will then be used by the members of the class for online sessions with the person who created the event. We do not share this information obtained throughout the OAuth process with any third-party tools.

If you no longer wish for us to be connected to your Google Calendar account, you can visit your Google account connection page at the following link [https://myaccount.google.com/connections](https://myaccount.google.com/connections) or contact us:  
Call us at: +1 (450) 680-1448  
Or write to us: [https://www.robotel.com/contact/](https://www.robotel.com/contact/)  

---------------------------

Our Company would like to send you information about our products and services that we think you might like, as well as those of our partner companies. If you have agreed to receive marketing, you may always opt-out at a later date.

You have the right at any time to stop Robotel from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your data to other members of Our Company Group.

If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please click the following link [https://www.robotel.com/contact/](https://www.robotel.com/contact/) or click on unsubscribe on our marketing emails 

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Our Company would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

The right to access - You have the right to request Our Company for copies of your personal data. 

The right to rectification - You have the right to request that Our Company correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request Our Company to complete information you believe is incomplete.

The right to erasure — You have the right to request that Our Company erase your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to restrict processing - You have the right to request that Our Company restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to object to processing - You have the right to object to Our Company’s processing  of your personal data, under certain conditions

The right to data portability - You have the right to request that Our Company transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at our email:

Call us at: +1 (450) 680-1448  
Or write to us: [https://www.robotel.com/contact/](https://www.robotel.com/contact/)

------------------------------------------

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you automatically through cookies or similar technology. We will ask you to accept those cookies.

For further information, visit aIIaboutcookies.org.

----------------------------------------------------

Our Company uses cookies in a range of ways to improve your experience on our website, including:

* Keeping you signed in
* Understanding how you use our website

------------------------------------------------------------------------

There are several different types of cookies, however, our website uses:

* Functionality — Our Company uses these cookies so that we recognize you on our website and remember your previously selected preferences. These could include what language you prefer and the location you are in. A mix of first-party and third-party cookies is used.
* Advertising — Our Company uses these cookies to collect information about your visit to our website, the content you viewed, the links you followed, and information about your browser, device, and IP address. Our Company sometimes shares some limited aspects of this data with third parties for advertising purposes. We may also share online data collected through cookies with our advertising partners. This means that when you visit another website, you may be shown advertising based on your browsing patterns on our website.

---------------------------------------------------

You can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------

The Robotel website contains links to other websites. Our privacy policy applies only to our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.

-------------------------------------------------------------------

Robotel keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on _Febuary 1st 2024_.

-------------------------------------------

If you have any questions about Our Company’s privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us.

Call us:  +1 (450) 680-1448

Or write to us at [https://www.robotel.com/contact/](https://www.robotel.com/contact/)

**How to contact the appropriate authority**

**For any type of complaint or if you feel like our company hasn’t addressed your concern please [contact us](https://www.robotel.com/contact/).** 

 +1 450 680-1448  
+1 (800) 680-1448
-----------------------------------

3185 Delaunay Laval, QC (Canada) H7L5A4

Solutions  

2024 Robotel. All Rights Reserved. [Privacy Policy](https://www.robotel.com/privacy-policy/)  -  [Terms of Use](https://www.robotel.com/terms-of-use)
